[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary", "Michael Skakel"]}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "Why has this happened?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "has", "this", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "Well, the judge in this case decided to go with what was effectively a Hail Mary path, because Michael Skakel has tried many times to overturn his guilty verdict.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "judge", "in", "this", "case", "decided", "to", "go", "with", "what", "was", "effectively", "a", "Hail", "Mary", "path", ",", "because", "Michael", "Skakel", "has", "tried", "many", "times", "to", "overturn", "his", "guilty", "verdict", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "I want to just get your reactions to what has happened today with this news that they maybe a new trial?", "question_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "just", "get", "your", "reactions", "to", "what", "has", "happened", "today", "with", "this", "news", "that", "they", "maybe", "a", "new", "trial", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Oh, my reaction.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "reaction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Yes, what is your reaction to this development?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "what", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "this", "development", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, first of all, there's not a way they can erase what was said during the first trial.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "there", "'s", "not", "a", "way", "they", "can", "erase", "what", "was", "said", "during", "the", "first", "trial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mickey Sherman"]}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "Is that something that makes you angry?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "something", "that", "makes", "you", "angry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Well, if I think about it being angry, but you know, Mickey Sherman did a wonderful job at that trial.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "I", "think", "about", "it", "being", "angry", ",", "but", "you", "know", ",", "Mickey", "Sherman", "did", "a", "wonderful", "job", "at", "that", "trial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Kennedy"]}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "What would you say to Robert F. Kennedy and indeed the wider Kennedy family who clearly share this view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "to", "Robert", "F.", "Kennedy", "and", "indeed", "the", "wider", "Kennedy", "family", "who", "clearly", "share", "this", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "You know, I don't believe that Robert Kennedy came to the trial very much.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "believe", "that", "Robert", "Kennedy", "came", "to", "the", "trial", "very", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert F. Kennedy", "Kennedy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Did you, Mrs. Moxley, have never had a shred of doubts in your mind that Michael Skakel was the person who killed your daughter?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", ",", "Mrs.", "Moxley", ",", "have", "never", "had", "a", "shred", "of", "doubts", "in", "your", "mind", "that", "Michael", "Skakel", "was", "the", "person", "who", "killed", "your", "daughter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Once we knew who it was.", "answer_tokens": ["Once", "we", "knew", "who", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Moxley", "Michael Skakel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "How have you coped over the years and how do you cope today?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "coped", "over", "the", "years", "and", "how", "do", "you", "cope", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "You know something, there are wonderful, wonderful people in this world.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "something", ",", "there", "are", "wonderful", ",", "wonderful", "people", "in", "this", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Now what I was asking really Moxley, when was how you personally as Martha's mother have coped with her horrendous death over the last four decades?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "what", "I", "was", "asking", "really", "Moxley", ",", "when", "was", "how", "you", "personally", "as", "Martha", "'s", "mother", "have", "coped", "with", "her", "horrendous", "death", "over", "the", "last", "four", "decades", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "OXLEY: You know because I've had such wonderful people who have helped me.", "answer_tokens": ["OXLEY", ":", "You", "know", "because", "I", "'ve", "had", "such", "wonderful", "people", "who", "have", "helped", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Martha"], "PERSON": ["Moxley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Do you think about the legality of what has happened?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "about", "the", "legality", "of", "what", "has", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, you know, one of the most common things that defendants raise after the trial is my lawyer did a bad job.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "one", "of", "the", "most", "common", "things", "that", "defendants", "raise", "after", "the", "trial", "is", "my", "lawyer", "did", "a", "bad", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "And given the proximity of time that is four decades after the death of this poor girl, can real justice still be attained after such a long period of time?", "question_tokens": ["And", "given", "the", "proximity", "of", "time", "that", "is", "four", "decades", "after", "the", "death", "of", "this", "poor", "girl", ",", "can", "real", "justice", "still", "be", "attained", "after", "such", "a", "long", "period", "of", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "It's going to be very difficult if they have to retrial the case because now there's been yet another 10 years have gone and this has passed away.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "very", "difficult", "if", "they", "have", "to", "retrial", "the", "case", "because", "now", "there", "'s", "been", "yet", "another", "10", "years", "have", "gone", "and", "this", "has", "passed", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "What do you feel about regurgitating all this so long after you've been in relation to her and her family?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "regurgitating", "all", "this", "so", "long", "after", "you", "'ve", "been", "in", "relation", "to", "her", "and", "her", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I have to tell you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "tell", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Is this Jeffrey Toobin?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "Jeffrey", "Toobin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeffrey Toobin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "What do we know about this case?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "we", "know", "about", "this", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Well, we know now the prosecutors are going to try him as an adult and that's going to be up to the grand jury to come back to decide whether or not they try him as an adult.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "know", "now", "the", "prosecutors", "are", "going", "to", "try", "him", "as", "an", "adult", "and", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "up", "to", "the", "grand", "jury", "to", "come", "back", "to", "decide", "whether", "or", "not", "they", "try", "him", "as", "an", "adult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "And the only clue at the moment was blood found in an upstairs room and that led them to find her body is that right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "only", "clue", "at", "the", "moment", "was", "blood", "found", "in", "an", "upstairs", "room", "and", "that", "led", "them", "to", "find", "her", "body", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ms. Ritzer"]}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What was your reaction to the news when you heard what had happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "to", "the", "news", "when", "you", "heard", "what", "had", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "When I had found out that Ms. Ritzer was murdered in the school it was devastating.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "had", "found", "out", "that", "Ms.", "Ritzer", "was", "murdered", "in", "the", "school", "it", "was", "devastating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "... Ms. Ritzer?", "question_tokens": ["...", "Ms.", "Ritzer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Oh, she was so kind.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "she", "was", "so", "kind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ms. Ritzer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "And Brianna what do we know about Philip Chism he was 14 years old, he was at your school did you -- did either of you know him particularly well?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Brianna", "what", "do", "we", "know", "about", "Philip", "Chism", "he", "was", "14", "years", "old", ",", "he", "was", "at", "your", "school", "did", "you", "--", "did", "either", "of", "you", "know", "him", "particularly", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "I didn't know him on a personal level but I had seem him around the hall and I knew that he was like really goof soccer player and people really liked him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "know", "him", "on", "a", "personal", "level", "but", "I", "had", "seem", "him", "around", "the", "hall", "and", "I", "knew", "that", "he", "was", "like", "really", "goof", "soccer", "player", "and", "people", "really", "liked", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brianna", "Philip Chism"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Paige, is anybody aware of any problems between him and Ms. Ritzer or any problems that he have with the school in general?", "question_tokens": ["Paige", ",", "is", "anybody", "aware", "of", "any", "problems", "between", "him", "and", "Ms.", "Ritzer", "or", "any", "problems", "that", "he", "have", "with", "the", "school", "in", "general", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "No, I didn't know anything of their relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "know", "anything", "of", "their", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paige", "Ms. Ritzer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "How are the students all dealing with it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "the", "students", "all", "dealing", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "NNPS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Can Kathleen Sebelius survive this if it continues to be a mess for weeks, months ahead?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "Kathleen", "Sebelius", "survive", "this", "if", "it", "continues", "to", "be", "a", "mess", "for", "weeks", ",", "months", "ahead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I think the best thing she has going for her is the fact that Republicans are calling for her head because there's nothing that President Obama dislikes more than Republicans calling for the firing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "best", "thing", "she", "has", "going", "for", "her", "is", "the", "fact", "that", "Republicans", "are", "calling", "for", "her", "head", "because", "there", "'s", "nothing", "that", "President", "Obama", "dislikes", "more", "than", "Republicans", "calling", "for", "the", "firing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathleen Sebelius"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Do you fear in your darkest moments that when you eventually live this mortal world of Oz that the headline maybe man who kept Dick Cheney alive in decades?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "fear", "in", "your", "darkest", "moments", "that", "when", "you", "eventually", "live", "this", "mortal", "world", "of", "Oz", "that", "the", "headline", "maybe", "man", "who", "kept", "Dick", "Cheney", "alive", "in", "decades", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "I'll wear it proudly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "wear", "it", "proudly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Cheney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "I've never meet Dick Cheney but obviously he's got this very tough reputation, very hard politician in anyway, very divisive, what was he like when he's going through such quite regular life and death scenarios in his own private life?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "never", "meet", "Dick", "Cheney", "but", "obviously", "he", "'s", "got", "this", "very", "tough", "reputation", ",", "very", "hard", "politician", "in", "anyway", ",", "very", "divisive", ",", "what", "was", "he", "like", "when", "he", "'s", "going", "through", "such", "quite", "regular", "life", "and", "death", "scenarios", "in", "his", "own", "private", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Incredibly courageous.", "answer_tokens": ["Incredibly", "courageous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Cheney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Tell me this, should somebody who is that sick or potentially could be fatally taken anytime, should they be vice president, were you concerned that actually he maybe old to stand out?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "this", ",", "should", "somebody", "who", "is", "that", "sick", "or", "potentially", "could", "be", "fatally", "taken", "anytime", ",", "should", "they", "be", "vice", "president", ",", "were", "you", "concerned", "that", "actually", "he", "maybe", "old", "to", "stand", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", ",", "MD", "VB", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "No, I wasn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "was", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Cheney"]}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "``", "UH", "PRP$", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Did it bring back memories to you a precisely the kind of thing that you feared?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "it", "bring", "back", "memories", "to", "you", "a", "precisely", "the", "kind", "of", "thing", "that", "you", "feared", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "You know, I actually didn't see it then I have seen it, but the night that it was broadcast Mrs. Cheney e-mailed me and said, \"Oh my God did you see Homeland tonight they just killed the vice president by reprogramming his defibrillator.\"", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "actually", "did", "n't", "see", "it", "then", "I", "have", "seen", "it", ",", "but", "the", "night", "that", "it", "was", "broadcast", "Mrs.", "Cheney", "e-mailed", "me", "and", "said", ",", "``", "Oh", "my", "God", "did", "you", "see", "Homeland", "tonight", "they", "just", "killed", "the", "vice", "president", "by", "reprogramming", "his", "defibrillator", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "I've also been watching this other show Hostages ago with the similar plot line with the terrorist get to the surgeon was about to operate and were you ever concern that people might try and get to you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "also", "been", "watching", "this", "other", "show", "Hostages", "ago", "with", "the", "similar", "plot", "line", "with", "the", "terrorist", "get", "to", "the", "surgeon", "was", "about", "to", "operate", "and", "were", "you", "ever", "concern", "that", "people", "might", "try", "and", "get", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Katie, what an exciting day, you must have been bursting with excitement?", "question_tokens": ["Katie", ",", "what", "an", "exciting", "day", ",", "you", "must", "have", "been", "bursting", "with", "excitement", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "First thing, it was very exciting, I mean it was beautiful over here, the sun was shining and as you said, it was actually a really big day obviously for George but only the second time we've seen him since he emerged from the hospital up to his birth.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "thing", ",", "it", "was", "very", "exciting", ",", "I", "mean", "it", "was", "beautiful", "over", "here", ",", "the", "sun", "was", "shining", "and", "as", "you", "said", ",", "it", "was", "actually", "a", "really", "big", "day", "obviously", "for", "George", "but", "only", "the", "second", "time", "we", "'ve", "seen", "him", "since", "he", "emerged", "from", "the", "hospital", "up", "to", "his", "birth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "What was the idea behind this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "idea", "behind", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "It was to have, you know, everybody who has gone through rough times and hurdles that they have to jump over to come together and to, you know, just share our message that even though we might have things to jump over, you know, we roar.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "to", "have", ",", "you", "know", ",", "everybody", "who", "has", "gone", "through", "rough", "times", "and", "hurdles", "that", "they", "have", "to", "jump", "over", "to", "come", "together", "and", "to", ",", "you", "know", ",", "just", "share", "our", "message", "that", "even", "though", "we", "might", "have", "things", "to", "jump", "over", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "roar", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "You must be very proud of all the children that took part in this?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "be", "very", "proud", "of", "all", "the", "children", "that", "took", "part", "in", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "We are.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]